GIOCRISRAI GODOY

Data Scientist | Data Analyst | Data Engineer | Machine Learning Engineer

LinkedIn: <u>Giocrisrai Godoy</u> Github: <u>Giocrisrai</u>

Email: <u>contact@giocrisrai.com</u> Website: <u>giocrisrai.com</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Data science specialist with a focus on data engineering and machine learning. Expert in data cleaning and processing, development of data pipelines using the Kedro framework, and the implementation of optimization solutions and advanced analytics through artificial intelligence techniques.

SKILLS

Python 3

- Pandas, Numpy, Scikit-learn, Seaborn, Matplotlib, Kedro, Keras, TensorFlow, Hugging Face (Transfer Learning)
- PostgreSQL, MySQL
- Git, Github
 - Agile, SCRUM, Kanban
- Azure
- Teamwork
- Self-learning
- Mentoring
- Client Communication
- Self-discipline
- Curiosity

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Data Scientist, Alaya

November 2022 - Present

- Development of Machine Learning model evaluations in mining processes using the Kedro framework.
- Implementation of data pipelines and deployment on Azure services for database management.
- Generation of robust databases and deployment of packaged solutions.
- Review and optimization of Machine Learning models.

Development Engineer, Geogama

March 2019 - November 2022

- Improvement of data-based processes in the organization's technological area.
- Utilization of visualization tools such as Looker Studio and PowerBI.
- · Management of Agile methodology for projects.
- Development of time series using TensorFlow for business solutions.

EDUCATION

- Platzi Master: Data Scientist | Software Development (2022)
- UNIR: Master's degree in Artificial Intelligence (2020-2021)
- University of Chile: Revalidation of Civil Mechatronics Engineer (2019)
- UNEXPO: Mechatronics Engineer (2008-2013)

Languages

- · Spanish (Native)
- English (B1)

Certifications from Platzi in various areas related to data science and machine learning.